<Document>
  # I.P.C.

  ### Homeworld
  Earth, technically.

  ### Temperment
  IPC tend to be Analytical in nature, enjoying jobs and tasks that allow them to flex their curiosity and experiment with the world around them.

  ### Secondary Species of Interest
  Goblin - IPC's and Goblins tend to get along very well.  The nearly ubiquitious desire for learning from IPC mixing very well with the Goblin desire to just try new ideas.

  Slime People - IPC have a slight - and often totally uncalled for - fear of the Slimier members of crew, usually revolving around rumors of short circuting.

  Reptillians - Many IPC find the cold calculating nature that some of their reptillian crewmates to fall well in line with their own often analytical natures.


  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="MobIPCDummy" Caption="I.P.C."/>
  An IPC (short for Integrated Positronic Chassis) is a type of sentient robot and is considered an [color=yellow]independent individual[/color], meaning [color=red]they are not guided by any laws of robotics[/color]. IPCs cannot be hacked by Emags because they do not have to follow any predefined directives in their system. [color=red]IPCs are silicon-based beings, so doctors do not have the skills to repair them.[/color]

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PositronicBrain" Caption="Positronic Brain"/>
  </Box>
  Like borgs, IPCs have a positronic brain as their processing source. However, unlike them, IPCs can't be assembled. "It's cheaper to create a shell that obeys you than one that doesn't! *wink*"

  ### Perks
  IPCs have the following perks:
  - They are immune to [color=lime]toxins[/color], [color=yellow]drugs[/color], and [color=yellow]alcohol[/color].
  - They are also immune to the effects of [color=yellow]space[/color], [color=yellow]low pressure[/color], and [color=cyan]the cold[/color].
  - They do not need to eat, drink, or breathe.
  - They are easy to revive, just repair the damage and hit the "Restart" button in the right-click menu.
  - Their power cell can be swapped out with a self-charging one, to never need to recharge again!
  - They have a built-in [color=yellow]headset[/color] and do not need to carry one.
  - IPC specific chems work regardless of if they're alive or not.

  ### Drawbacks
  IPCs have the following drawbacks:
  - They are vulnerable to [color=yellow]EMP[/color] damage, which will drain your battery.
  - They are slowed by low battery, by up to 90% at 0 charge.
  - They take [color=orange]double damage from heat,[/color] and can be set on fire more easily.
  - Their topicals are specialized, storage inefficient, and relatively expensive.
  - They need IPC specific chems to be healed.
  - They take [color=yellow]Structural[/color] damage, such as that from pickaxes, drills, and PKAs. However, they resist 50% of it after a flat reduction of 10.

  ## Recharging an IPC
   <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="APCBasic" Caption="APC Terminal"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="BorgCharger" Caption="Borg Charger"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PowerCellMedium" Caption="Power Cell"/>
  </Box>
  IPCs can be recharged in three different ways:

  APC Terminal: IPCs can use APC terminals to recharge. Press [color=yellow]Alt + left click[/color] on a terminal as many times as needed to fully recharge.

  Borg Rechargers: IPCs can use borg rechargers to recharge. Always prioritize the ones outside of the Sci area to avoid headaches.

  Power Cell: IPCs have an internal power cell that serves as their battery. They can simply swap it out by opening the hatch and manually replacing it.

  ## Integrated Radio
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="EncryptionKeyScience" Caption="Encryption key"/>
  </Box>

  IPCs can choose not to use external radios because they already have one built in. They only need to get an encryption key from a radio. By clicking on an IPC with a [color=yellow]wire cutter[/color], you can remove their keys.
  You can find new keys around the station or remove one from a sector radio using a [color=yellow]screwdriver[/color].

  ## Repairing
  <Box HorizontalAlignment="Stretch">
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RepairSpray" Caption="Repair Spray"/>
    Repair sprays are used to cure huge [color=pink]Slashing, Piercing[/color] damage, and [color=yellow]Structural[/color] damage too.
  </Box>
  <Box HorizontalAlignment="Stretch">
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RepairPatch" Caption="Repair Patch"/>
    Repair sprays are used to cure moderate [color=pink]Slashing, Piercing[/color] damage in a pinch, and light[color=yellow]Structural[/color] damage.
  </Box>
  <Box HorizontalAlignment="Stretch">
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="WelderIndustrialAdvanced" Caption="Welder"/>
    Welders can be used to repair [color=pink]Blunt[/color] damage, and low [color=yellow]structural[/color] damage too.
  </Box>
  <Box HorizontalAlignment="Stretch">
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CableApcStack" Caption="Cables (any type)"/>
    Cables can be used to repair light [color=orange]Burns[/color] in an emergency, low [color=yellow]Structural[/color] damage too.
  </Box>
  <Box HorizontalAlignment="Stretch">
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="RepairAutoinjector" Caption="Emergency Repair autoinjector: contains 20u of Autosolder!"/>
    Autosolder is used to repair [color=yellow]Blindness and Structural[/color], [color=lime]Radiation[/color], major [color=orange]Burns.[/color].
  </Box>
    In the event an IPC dies, after being fully repaired, it should be restarted using the [color=yellow]"Restart"[/color] button (located by right-clicking).

    [color=red]DO NOT DEFIBRILLATE OR SHOCK A DEAD IPC. They'll explode and probably kill you too![/color]

</Document>
