<Document>
  # PETREL-CLASS CARGO TUG
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CrateTradeSecureHigh" Caption="trading crate"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CrateGenericSteel" Caption="mystery loot"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="OreProcessor"/>
  </Box>

    [color=#a4885c]Ship Size:[/color] Medium

	[color=#a4885c]Recommended Crew:[/color] 2-4

	[color=#a4885c]Power Gen Type:[/color] Uranium

	[color=#a4885c]Expeditions:[/color] No

	[color=#a4885c]IFF Console:[/color] None

  "A medium sized space forklift from the USSP-based Kesha Aerospace Plant, with a massive vacuum-exposed cargo rack ready to shove station-constructing loads of material wherever you need it to go!"
  
  "The Petrel is designed around two unique components; the ship itself, which is based on an old tug design, and the large vacuum-exposed cargo rack. Be sure to wear EVA gear when operating the Emu PLUs!"

  # PREFLIGHT CHECKLIST

  ## 1. Power supply

  ## 1.1. Battery units
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SMESBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SubstationBasic"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="APCBasic"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the SMES unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the substation unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check that the APC unit's Main Breaker is toggled on.
  - Check the APC unit's current Load* (W).

  ## 1.2. S.U.P.E.R.P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PortableGeneratorSuperPacman"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SheetUranium"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="SignRadiationMed"/>
  </Box>
  
  - Open radiation shielding.
  - Check if the S.U.P.E.R.P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit is anchored to the floor.
  - Check if the S.U.P.E.R.P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit has fuel. For extended flights make sure that you have enough fuel stockpiled to sustain prolonged power generation during flight.
  - Check if the S.U.P.E.R.P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit is set to HV output.
  - Set Target Power for 40 [bold]k[/bold]W.
  - Start the S.U.P.E.R.P.A.C.M.A.N. generator unit.
  - Close radiation shielding.

  ## 2. Atmospherics

  ## 2.1. Distribution Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="OxygenCanister"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="NitrogenCanister"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPort"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasMixer"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the O2 canister is anchored to connector port.
  - Check that the N2 canister is anchored to connector port.
  - Check that the gas mixer is set to the correct mixing ratio (21% Oxygen, 79% Nitrogen).
  - Check that the gas mixer is set to 101kPa.
  - Enable gas mixer.

  ## 2.2. Waste Loop
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GasPressurePump"/>
  </Box>

  - Enable waste loop pump (located in ore silo/gyroscope room).

  ## 3. Other checks
  <Box>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="Gyroscope"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="GravityGeneratorMini"/>
  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="BlastDoor"/>
  </Box>

  - Check that the gyroscope is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  - Check that the mini gravity generator is anchored, powered, and enabled.
  - Ensure shutter and bolt switches are functional.

</Document>
